[The Epoch of Miyu]
[미유시대]
[Episode 18]
[18화]
Mr. Ji,
지 선생님,
Ms. Xu is here.
Ms. Xu가 여기 있습니다.
Let her in.
그녀를 들여보내주세요.
Do you know why I called you here?
내가 왜 당신을 여기로 불렀는지 아세요?
Yes.
예.
Because the morning shoot was delayed.
오전 촬영이 늦어졌기 때문이죠.
Delayed?
지연?
I specifically reminded you the day before,
내가 구체적으로 상기시켜줬어 전날
and repeatedly stressed that the crew
그리고 그것을 거듭 강조했다. 승무원
would arrive at 8:00.
8시에 도착할 거야.
What time did you arrive?
몇 시에 도착하셨나요?
Xu Miyu,
쉬 미유,
as a forewoman,
감독으로서
can you not even fulfill such a simple request
너도 이행하지 못하겠니? 이렇게 간단한 요청이군요
from a guest?
손님에게서?
I arrived at 7:30
7시 30분에 도착했어요
and kept reminding them.
그리고 계속해서 그들에게 상기시켰습니다.
What's the use of just reminding them?
단지 그들에게 상기시켜 주면 무슨 소용이 있겠습니까?
David already said it—
데이빗이 이미 말했어요—
there was so much luggage
짐이 너무 많았어
piled up in the presidential suite,
대통령실에 쌓여있어
and the butlers were going in and out, yet no one cleaned it up.
집사들이 드나들고 있었고, 그러나 아무도 그것을 청소하지 않았습니다.
Ultimately,
결국
the delay was caused by your irresponsible service.
지연이 발생했습니다 당신의 무책임한 서비스로 인해.
The guest had 14 suitcases in total.
손님은 총 14개의 여행가방을 가지고 있었습니다.
Every suitcase
모든 여행가방
was filled with her private clothes and personal items.
그녀의 사복들로 가득 차 있었어 그리고 개인 물품.
Without the guest's permission,
손님의 허락 없이
we cannot touch any of that luggage.
우리는 그 짐을 만질 수 없습니다.
Couldn't you have just asked David?
방금 데이비드에게 물어볼 수는 없었나요?
I couldn't reach him all day yesterday.
어제 하루종일 그 사람한테 연락이 안 됐어요.
Mr. Ji,
지 선생님,
with this attitude of hers,
그녀의 이런 태도로
I really can't work with her.
난 정말 그녀와 함께 일할 수 없습니다.
Besides,
게다가,
Qiao Feifei has been contacting me.
Qiao Feifei가 나에게 연락했습니다.
I should have first arranged a VIP parking space
내가 먼저 했어야 했는데 VIP 주차 공간을 마련했어
and the massage package for her.
그리고 그녀를 위한 마사지 패키지.
If it really doesn't work out, I...
정말 안되면...
Come to me anytime.
언제든지 나에게로 오세요.
Do you feel wronged?
당신은 부당하다고 생각합니까?
No.
아니요.
But I did look for David.
하지만 나는 데이빗을 찾았어요.
I couldn't find him.
나는 그를 찾을 수 없었다.
We are not discussing
우리는 논의하고 있지 않습니다
whether a room butler
방집사인지
should tell a guest in advance
손님에게 미리 말해야 해
to prepare their clothes for the next day,
다음날 입을 옷을 준비하기 위해
nor are we judging whether you actually did enough
우리가 판단하는 것도 아니고 실제로 충분히 했는지
from yesterday until now.
어제부터 지금까지.
Because
왜냐하면
it has already happened.
그것은 이미 일어났습니다.
When facing a problem,
문제가 발생하면
don't waste your time
시간 낭비하지 마세요
dwelling on emotions.
감정에 머물다.
Instead, you should quickly
대신, 빨리
find a solution.
해결책을 찾으세요.
Truly good service
정말 좋은 서비스
isn't just acting polite.
단지 예의바르게 행동하는 것이 아니다.
It's about having the real ability to solve problems decisively.
진짜 능력이 있다는 얘기죠 문제를 과감하게 해결하는 것.
I understand.
이해합니다.
Recently,
최근
the famous actress Li Bingyan, who had retired for years,
유명한 여배우 리빙옌(Li Bingyan), 수년간 은퇴한 사람
has gone public with her relationship.
그녀의 관계가 공개되었습니다.
At the Purong Hotel in Shanghai,
상하이 푸롱 호텔에서
she showed affection with her younger boyfriend,
그녀는 애정을 보였다 어린 남자친구와
causing heated discussions among netizens.
네티즌들 사이에서 열띤 토론을 벌이고 있다.
Originally participating alone
원래 혼자 참여 중
in the show "Begin Again",
"Begin Again" 쇼에서
she
그녀는
now has to be accompanied by an assistant
이제 보조자가 동행해야 합니다
and escorted by security.
보안요원의 호위를 받았습니다.
Her net worth skyrocketed overnight.
그녀의 순자산은 하룻밤 사이에 급등했습니다.
It is said that
It is said that
the show's production team has already designated her
드라마 제작팀 이미 그녀를 지정했어
as a regular guest for the next two seasons.
단골 손님으로 다음 두 시즌 동안.
Zhenzhen,
젠젠,
when you begged me
네가 나한테 애원했을 때
to bring our Feifei
우리 Feifei를 데려오려고요
to stay at your Purong,
푸롱에 머물고 싶다면
I believed in your sincerity.
나는 당신의 진심을 믿었습니다.
But what is the result?
그러나 결과는 무엇입니까?
I put in so much effort
정말 많은 노력을 기울였어
to arrange media exposure for our Feifei.
Feifei에 대한 미디어 노출을 준비합니다.
In one instant, it was all stolen by that person surnamed Li.
한순간에 다 훔쳐갔어 Li라는 사람이요.
Just like that, their side gained countless new followers.
그런 식으로, 그들의 편은 수많은 새로운 추종자를 얻었습니다.
Our Feifei's star power,
우리 페이페이의 스타파워,
the kind that can stir up huge traffic,
엄청난 트래픽을 유발할 수 있는 종류
is not meant to be someone else's stepping stone.
다른 사람의 것이 될 수는 없습니다 디딤돌.
Tell me, as a top sales rep,
최고 영업 담당자로서 말해 보세요.
how do you do your job?
당신은 일을 어떻게 하시나요?
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
It's already good enough that I didn't go looking for you.
이미 충분히 괜찮아 내가 당신을 찾으러 가지 않았다는 걸요.
How dare you come over here
감히 여기까지 오다니
and talk to me about a fan meet-and-greet?
팬미팅에 대해 얘기해 주실래요?
Do you think
네 생각엔
there's any chance of us cooperating again?
가능성은 있어 우리 또 협력하는 거야?
Wei, I'm really sorry.
웨이, 정말 미안해요.
Really sorry.
정말 미안해요.
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
I need to take a call.
전화를 받아야 해요.
Got it.
알았어요.
I'm coming.
나는 간다.
Calm down, Wei.
진정해, 웨이.
I'll find another chance
또 다른 기회를 찾아볼게
to win one back for Feifei.
Feifei를 위해 다시 승리합니다.
Don't you trust me?
당신은 나를 믿지 않습니까?
Ms. Lu.
루 씨.
Mr. Ji wants to see me.
지 선생님이 저를 보고 싶어 하세요.
[General Manager's Office]
[부장실]
Come in.
들어오세요.
Sorry, I'm late.
미안해요, 늦었어요.
Come here.
이리 오세요.
Let me introduce you.
소개하겠습니다.
This is
이것은
Ms. Brown,
브라운 씨,
the Commercial Director
상업 이사
of Liberty Group.
리버티 그룹의.
You're the woman
당신이 그 여자예요
who inspired Marcos, aren't you?
마르코스에게 영감을 준 사람이 누구죠?
You're amazing.
당신은 정말 대단해요.
You know that he wouldn't stop speaking about you
그 사람이 멈추지 않을 거라는 걸 알잖아 당신에 대해 말하는 중
until I came here.
내가 여기 오기 전까지는.
Please.
제발.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
As everything I should have done,
내가 모든 일을 했어야 했듯이,
I always put my clients' demands first,
나는 항상 고객의 요구를 최우선으로 생각합니다.
and we're honored to reach Marcos' standards.
그리고 우리는 영광입니다 마르코스의 기준에 도달하세요.
I promise
약속해요
we will continue to provide the best service
우리는 계속해서 제공할 것입니다 최고의 서비스
to you and members of your company.
귀하와 귀하의 회사 구성원에게.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Oh.
오.
Let me extend Marcos' gratitude from him.
그에게 마르코스의 감사를 전하겠습니다.
If I may?
내가 할 수 있다면?
It's yours.
그것은 당신 것입니다.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Dear Ms. Xu,
친애하는 Ms. Xu님,
I feel so lucky
정말 행운인 것 같아
to have enjoyed your incredible butler service
즐겼다 당신의 놀라운 집사 서비스
at Purong Hotel in Shanghai, China.
중국 상하이 푸롱 호텔에서
My visit to the archives before leaving
떠나기 전에 기록 보관소를 방문했습니다
was the highlight of my entire trip to China.
하이라이트였어 나의 중국 여행 내내.
Thanks for your insight and warmth,
귀하의 통찰력과 따뜻함에 감사드립니다.
making me feel your genuine service
당신의 진정한 서비스를 느끼게 해주세요
and care.
그리고 배려.
I hope my team
내 팀이 희망해
can enjoy your amazing hospitality in the future.
당신의 즐길 수 있습니다 앞으로도 놀라운 환대를 부탁드립니다.
Yours sincerely, Marcos Yang.
진심으로 감사드립니다, 마르코스 양.
It is my pleasure.
그것은 나의 기쁨입니다.
You deserve it.
당신은 그럴 자격이 있습니다.
Thanks to Marcos and you.
마르코스와 당신에게 감사드립니다.
Thank you so much.
매우 감사합니다.
[Internal Office] [Convention Center]
[사내사무실] [컨벤션센터]
I'm looking forward for a strong
강한 모습을 기대하고 있어요
and long cooperation.
그리고 오랜 협력.
I'm flattered, honestly.
솔직히 기쁘네요.
Ms. Xu, it's very nice to meet you.
Xu 선생님, 만나서 정말 반가워요.
Hope to see you again.
다시 만나기를 바랍니다.
Definitely. We've just signed the contract
분명히. 우리는 방금 계약서에 서명했어요
so you will definitely see me again.
그러니 당신은 반드시 나를 다시 보게 될 것입니다.
I'm looking forward to this great service
나는 기대하고있다 이 훌륭한 서비스에
next time I come.
다음에 오면.
Thank you very much.
매우 감사합니다.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Secretary Wu,
우 비서
see her out.
그녀를 만나보세요.
Okay.
좋아요.
-Thank you. -Okay.
-감사합니다. -좋아요.
[Internal Office] [Convention Center]
[사내사무실] [컨벤션센터]
Mr. Ji,
지 선생님,
I also put a lot of effort
나도 노력을 많이 했어
into this order.
이 순서대로.
I didn't mean to steal Ms. Xu's credit.
나는 Xu 씨의 신용을 훔칠 생각이 없었습니다.
Post card.
엽서.
[Internal Office] [Convention Center]
[사내사무실] [컨벤션센터]
Can you handle it well?
잘 처리할 수 있나요?
I can.
나는 할 수 있다.
I'll trust you one more time.
한 번만 더 믿어보겠습니다.
Did you arrange
준비했나요
these dishes?
이 요리들?
I'm glad you like them.
마음에 드셨다니 기쁘네요.
I don't care what ingredients you use.
어떤 재료를 사용하든 상관없습니다.
If this noodle dish fails,
이 국수 요리가 실패하면
will you take responsibility?
책임질래?
I will.
그럴게요.
Actually,
실제로
your butler is also
네 집사도
an excellent chef.
훌륭한 요리사.
Today's plain noodles were made by her.
오늘의 생면은 그녀가 만들어준 것입니다.
I really finished
정말 끝냈어
the plain noodles.
평범한 국수.
With an attitude like hers,
그녀와 같은 태도로
I really can't work with her.
난 정말 그녀와 함께 일할 수 없습니다.
If it really doesn't work out, I...
정말 안되면...
Contact me anytime.
언제든지 저에게 연락하세요.
Postcard.
엽서.
If you want to be like before,
예전처럼 되고 싶다면
you have to live more strongly than anyone else.
넌 좀 더 살아야 해 누구보다 강하게.
You have to learn how to climb higher,
너는 더 높이 올라가는 법을 배워야 해,
learn how to fight, and learn how to take what's yours.
싸우는 법을 배우고, 그리고 당신의 것을 가져가는 방법을 배우십시오.
You must make everyone who looked down on you
모두를 만들어야 해 누가 당신을 무시했나요
[Young Lu Zhenzhen]
[영 루 젠젠]
regret it!
후회해!
Understand?
이해하다?
Regarding the fan meeting,
팬미팅 관련해서
the agency has no intention of cooperating,
소속사는 의도가 없다 협력의
so I'm afraid I have to apologize.
그래서 사과해야 할 것 같아요.
Ms. Lu,
루 선생님,
can you let us go upstairs
can you let us go upstairs
to see Feifei just once?
우리를 위층으로 올라가게 해줄 수 있나요
Name your price.
페이페이 한 번만 만나볼까?
Feifei is a very important client of mine.
가격을 지정하세요.
How could I ruin my career
Feifei는 제게 매우 중요한 고객입니다.
for a little money?
어떻게 내 경력을 망칠 수 있니
Then, Ms. Lu,
약간의 돈 때문에?
is Li Bingyan also your important client?
그럼, 루 선생님,
What do you mean?
Li Bingyan도 중요한 고객인가요?
We're just worried about Feifei.
무슨 뜻이에요?
That Li is not popular,
우리는 단지 Feifei가 걱정될 뿐입니다.
but she loves to clout-chase.
그 Li는 인기가 없어
Our Feifei is beautiful and kind,
하지만 그녀는 영향력을 행사하는 것을 좋아합니다.
and can't do anything to her.
우리 페이페이는 아름답고 친절해요
But as her fans,
그리고 그녀에게 아무것도 할 수 없습니다.
we have an obligation to get justice for her.
하지만 그녀의 팬으로서
That's right.
우리에게는 의무가 있다 그녀를 위해 정의를 얻기 위해.
We promise not to disturb Sister Feifei,
좋아요.
but we must get revenge.
우리는 페이페이 자매를 방해하지 않기로 약속합니다.
You three can't go up to the presidential suite.
하지만 우리는 복수를 해야 해요.
You need to swipe a card to go up,
너희 셋은 못 올라가 대통령 스위트 룸으로.
and you also need to register.
올라가려면 카드를 스와이프해야 합니다.
Especially since two big stars are staying up there right now,
등록도 해야 합니다.
the security is very strict.
특히 두 명의 빅스타 이후로 지금 거기 머물고 있어
Ms. Lu, you are very resourceful.
보안이 매우 엄격합니다.
We all think you're amazing.
루 씨, 당신은 매우 재주가 많습니다.
You must have a way.
우리 모두는 당신이 훌륭하다고 생각합니다.
I really don't have a way.
방법이 있어야합니다.
I'm sorry.
정말 방법이 없어요.
You must have a way, Ms. Lu.
죄송합니다.
Otherwise, how could you become
방법이 있으실 겁니다, 루 씨.
the VIP Account Manager of Purong Hotel?
그렇지 않으면 어떻게
Exactly.
푸롱 호텔의 VIP 계정 관리자?
You three are quite sweet-talkers,
정확히.
and your intelligence gathering is quite impressive.
너희 셋은 꽤 다정한 대화를 나누는구나,
Seeing that you have such deep sisterhood
그리고 당신의 정보 수집 꽤 인상적이다.
with your sister,
이렇게 깊은 자매애를 갖고 있는 걸 보니
I can help you.
네 여동생과 함께
But promise me,
제가 도와드릴 수 있어요.
not to mention my name to anyone.
하지만 약속해 주세요.
We promise not to tell.
누구에게도 내 이름을 언급하지 마세요.
[Duan Aoxiang, 1825]
우리는 말하지 않겠다고 약속합니다.
If we handle him,
[단아오샹, 1825년]
can we get into the presidential suite?
우리가 그를 처리하면,
We'll check into the executive floor right away.
우리 대통령실로 들어갈 수 있나요?
Let's go.
갑시다.
Hello.
안녕하세요.
Daniel.
다니엘.
Where are you going? Going out?
어디 가세요? 외출?
I'm going on a date.
나는 데이트를 할 예정이다.
Who are you dating?
당신은 누구와 데이트하고 있습니까?
Why not invite him to your hotel room?
그를 호텔 방으로 초대해 보는 것은 어떨까요?
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
Did Old Madam send you
늙은 부인이 당신에게 보냈나요
to spy on me?
나를 염탐하려고?
No.
아니요.
I'm just afraid you'll miss your medicine.
나는 단지 당신이 약을 놓치게 될까 두렵습니다.
Don't worry.
괜찮아요.
Ming,
밍
my old friend, is back from Shenzhen.
나의 오랜 친구가 심천에서 돌아왔습니다.
I'm going to see him.
나는 그를 만나러 갈 것이다.
Take it easy.
진정하세요.
Behind you!
당신 뒤에!
Bro, do you know how to defend the tower?
형, 탑을 방어하는 방법을 아세요?
Seriously…
정말...
Are you stupid?
당신은 바보인가요?
Mr. Duan.
듀안 씨.
Run!
달리다!
You can't beat him.
당신은 그를 이길 수 없습니다.
Someone is watching you.
누군가가 당신을 지켜보고 있습니다.
Where?
어디?
The direction is from your four o'clock.
방향은 4시 방향입니다.
It looks like the other side disconnected.
반대쪽 연결이 끊어진 것 같습니다.
Does it?
그렇습니까?
Did you get a clear look?
깔끔하게 보셨나요?
Is he really Duan Aoxiang?
그는 정말 Duan Aoxiang인가요?
Yes.
예.
Am I this popular now?
내가 지금 이렇게 인기가 있는 걸까?
Duan...
두안...
Duan Aoxiang!
두안 아오샹!
Who are you?
누구세요?
Who sent you to tail me?
누가 나를 미행하라고 당신을 보냈나요?
We...
우리는...
We weren't sent to tail you.
우리는 당신을 미행하기 위해 파견되지 않았습니다.
We are Qiao Feifei's fans.
우리는 Qiao Feifei의 팬입니다.
We want to go upstairs to find Li Bingyan
Li Bingyan을 찾기 위해 위층으로 올라가고 싶습니다
to avenge Feifei.
페이페이의 복수를 위해.
We need your help.
여러분의 도움이 필요합니다.
Qiao Feifei's fans
Qiao Feifei의 팬
came to find Li Bingyan?
Li Bingyan을 찾으러 왔나요?
Interesting.
흥미로운.
Ms. Xu.
쉬 씨.
Mr. Tan, are you here to see Daniel?
탄 씨, 다니엘을 만나러 오셨나요?
I also dropped by to see you.
나도 당신을 만나러 들렀어요.
I just went to my dad's room to look for him.
방금 아빠 방에 갔어. 그를 찾으러.
He doesn't seem to be here.
그는 여기에 없는 것 같습니다.
Do you know where he went?
그 사람이 어디로 갔는지 아세요?
Mr. Tan seems to have gone out.
탄 씨는 나간 것 같습니다.
Did you
Did you
call him?
그에게 전화해?
He went out?
그가 나갔나요?
I called him,
그 사람에게 전화했어요
but he isn't answering.
하지만 그는 대답하지 않습니다.
Could something have happened to him?
그에게 무슨 일이 일어났을까요?
Daniel!
다니엘!
Dad!
아빠!
It seems he hasn't returned yet.
그 사람은 아직 돌아오지 않은 것 같군요.
Where did he go?
그는 어디로 갔습니까?
He hasn't answered his phone all day.
그는 하루 종일 전화를 받지 않았습니다.
Mr. Tan, don't worry.
탄 씨, 걱정하지 마세요.
I remember
기억나네
Daniel said when he left this afternoon
다니엘이 오늘 오후에 떠날 때 말했다
that he was going to see a friend named Ming.
그 사람이 할 예정이었어 Ming이라는 친구를 만나보세요.
Do you have Ming's phone number
밍 전화번호 아세요
or his address?
아니면 그 사람 주소?
Ming?
밍?
I don't.
나는 아니에요.
Wait, I think I've heard this name before.
잠깐만요, 이 이름은 들어본 적이 있는 것 같아요.
How about this?
이건 어때요?
I'll give Aunt Wanjun a call.
완준 이모한테 전화해볼게.
What?
무엇?
No one is at Ming's house.
Ming의 집에는 아무도 없습니다.
Mr. Tan, don't worry.
탄 씨, 걱정하지 마세요.
I know a place
나는 한 곳을 알아
that Mr. Tan mentioned to me before.
탄 선생님이 전에 나한테 말씀하셨던 거예요.
Wait a moment.
잠시만 기다려주세요.
I'll come find you
내가 널 찾으러 갈게
and take you there.
그리고 거기로 데려가세요.
You're on duty tonight.
당신은 오늘 밤 근무 중입니다.
I need to go out for a bit.
좀 나가야 해요.
The presidential suite has no special arrangements tonight.
프레지덴셜 스위트룸 오늘 밤에는 특별한 약속이 없어요.
Don't go up there rashly.
함부로 거기 올라가지 마세요.
If there are any emergencies,
긴급 상황이 발생하면
contact me immediately.
즉시 연락주세요.
Okay.
좋아요.
By the way,
그런데,
if Mr. Tan comes back,
탄 씨가 돌아오면
call me right away.
지금 당장 전화해.
Okay.
좋아요.
Hello.
안녕하세요.
Executive floor receptionist.
이그제큐티브 플로어 접수원.
Please wait a moment.
잠시만 기다려주세요.
I'll be right there.
나는 바로 거기에 있을 것이다.
Thank you, Mr. Duan.
고마워요, 두안 씨.
Keep a low profile.
낮은 프로필을 유지하십시오.
Mr. Duan,
두안 씨,
are we really letting them go up?
우리가 정말 그들을 위로 놔두는 걸까요?
What if they cause trouble?
문제를 일으키면 어떻게 되나요?
Isn't it better if they cause trouble?
문제를 일으키면 더 좋지 않나요?
Ji Feng gave me this red carpet gift package.
지펑이 나한테 줬어 이번 레드카펫 선물 패키지.
I was just worrying about what to give him in return.
그냥 걱정하고 있었어 그 대가로 그에게 무엇을 줄 것인가.
Let's go.
갑시다.
Let's go home and enjoy the show.
집에 가서 공연을 즐기자.
Feifei is right here.
Feifei가 바로 여기 있습니다.
Yes.
예.
We must find Li Bingyan today!
오늘은 Li Bingyan을 찾아야합니다!
Who are you?
누구세요?
How did you get up here?
어떻게 여기까지 올라왔나요?
It's Li Bingyan.
리빙옌입니다.
Mr. Tan!
탄 씨!
Here.
여기.
Sir,
선생님,
wake up.
깨우다.
Sir.
선생님.
Dad.
아빠.
Dad, wake up.
아빠, 일어나세요.
Is Mr. Tan alright?
탄 씨는 괜찮으세요?
Sir,
선생님,
Get up and come home with me.
일어나서 나와 함께 집에 가세요.
[Luo Qingping]
[뤄칭핑]
Wake up.
깨우다.
Get up.
일어나세요.
Can you get up?
일어날 수 있나요?
We're going home.
우리는 집에 갈거야.
He is sleeping soundly.
그는 푹 자고 있습니다.
Thanks a lot for today.
오늘 정말 고마워요.
How did you know they'd go there?
그들이 거기로 갈 것이라는 것을 어떻게 알았나요?
Mr. Tan mentioned to me before
탄 선생님이 전에 나한테 말씀하셨어
that there was a jazz bar
재즈 바가 있었다고
he really liked.
그는 정말 좋아했습니다.
Right.
오른쪽.
The jazz band's first performance
재즈 밴드의 첫 공연
was also there.
거기에도 있었어요.
So I figured
그래서 나는
it must be that place.
그 곳임에 틀림없어요.
You haven't known my father for long,
당신은 내 아버지를 오랫동안 알지 못했어요
yet you know him so well.
그런데 당신은 그 사람을 너무나 잘 알고 있어요.
Unlike me,
나와는 달리
I've lived with him for so many years,
나는 그 사람과 수년 동안 함께 살았어
but I act like an idiot.
하지만 난 바보처럼 행동해요.
I don't know his past,
나는 그 사람의 과거를 모른다
nor his preferences.
그의 취향도 아니다.
It's quite shameful.
참 부끄럽습니다.
Don't say that.
그렇게 말하지 마세요.
You are so busy with work.
당신은 일로 너무 바쁘다.
[Lu Zhenzhen]
[루 젠젠]
Hello?
안녕하세요?
[Luo Qingping] [Lu Zhenzhen]
[뤄 칭핑] [루 젠젠]
What's wrong?
무슨 일이야?
Are you okay?
괜찮으세요?
I have so many missed calls.
부재중 전화가 너무 많아요.
My phone was on silent.
내 전화기는 무음으로 되어 있었다.
Oh no.
안 돼.
Something must have happened at the hotel.
호텔에서 무슨 일이 있었나 봐요.
Don't worry.
괜찮아요.
Driver,
운전사,
please hurry.
서둘러 주세요.
We're in a rush.
우리는 서두르고 있습니다.
Okay.
좋아요.
Why is Li Bingyan hiding?
Li Bingyan은 왜 숨어 있습니까?
Is she afraid to take responsibility?
그녀는 책임을지기를 두려워합니까?
Stop shouting!
그만 소리쳐!
Calm down!
진정하다!
Everyone, calm down.
모두들 진정하세요.
-Let's talk this through properly; don't resort to violence. -Li Bingyan!
- 제대로 이야기해 봅시다. 폭력을 행사하지 마십시오. -리 빙옌!
Quiet!
조용한!
I'm calling the police.
경찰에 전화할게요.
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
Be careful.
조심하세요.
Keep your voices down.
목소리를 낮추세요.
Stop fighting!
그만 싸워라!
The general manager is here. Stop arguing!
총지배인이 여기 있습니다. 논쟁을 멈춰라!
Mr. Ji,
지 선생님,
you're finally here.
당신은 마침내 여기에 있습니다.
I've been trying to call Ms. Xu,
Xu 씨에게 전화를 걸려고 했어요
but I can't reach her.
하지만 나는 그녀에게 연락할 수 없어요.
Mr. Ji,
지 선생님,
I'll have someone arrange for them to go back and rest.
누군가에게 정리하라고 할게요 그들이 돌아가서 쉴 수 있도록.
After all, they are hotel guests.
결국 그들은 호텔 손님입니다.
I will personally investigate and question them later.
제가 직접 조사해보겠습니다 나중에 질문해 보세요.
Is that alright with you?
괜찮으세요?
Okay.
좋아요.
Ms. Xu,
쉬 선생님,
with such a major incident happening in the presidential suite,
이렇게 큰 사건이 일어나면서 대통령실에서
where did you go?
어디 갔어?
Do you know how many people couldn't reach you?
몇명인지 아시나요? 연락이 안 됐나요?
I went...
나는 갔다...
Ms. Xu,
쉬 선생님,
we have such important guests staying in the presidential suite,
이렇게 중요한 손님이 계시는데 대통령실에 머물면서
yet you
아직 너는
left them behind and ran off.
그들을 남겨두고 도망갔습니다.
You made everyone clean up your mess.
당신은 모두가 당신의 혼란을 정리하게 만들었습니다.
As the forewoman of the executive floor,
임원진의 수석으로서
are you competent?
당신은 능력이 있습니까?
Mr. Ji,
지 선생님,
you really shouldn't have
넌 정말 그러지 말았어야 했어
left such an important guest
이렇게 중요한 손님을 두고 왔어요
in her care.
그녀의 보살핌에.
It's too irresponsible.
너무 무책임해요.
Ms. Xu,
쉬 선생님,
your explanation?
당신의 설명은?
Mr. Tan in Room 1810
1810호실에 있는 탄 씨
suddenly went missing.
갑자기 실종되었습니다.
I took his family to look for him
나는 그의 가족을 데리고 그를 찾으러 갔어
and temporarily left my post.
일시적으로 내 게시물을 떠났습니다.
I apologize.
사과드립니다.
Where is he?
그는 어디에 있나요?
He has returned to his room to rest.
그는 휴식을 취하기 위해 자신의 방으로 돌아왔습니다.
Did you arrange a caregiver?
간병인을 배치하셨나요?
His family is with him.
그의 가족이 그와 함께 있습니다.
It's a matter of life and death,
이건 삶과 죽음의 문제야,
so it's indeed urgent.
그래서 정말 긴급해요.
Alright, Ms. Lu,
알겠습니다, 루 선생님,
go and comfort the guests first.
먼저 가서 손님들을 위로해 주십시오.
Yes,
네,
I'll go right now.
지금 바로 갈게요.
Ms. Xu,
쉬 선생님,
I said it's excusable,
변명의 여지가 있다고 말했는데,
but don't really think you're not at fault.
하지만 별로 생각하지 마세요 당신은 잘못이 없습니다.
You are the forewoman.
당신은 감독입니다.
Ensuring
보장
the normal operation of the executive floor
정상적인 작동 임원 층의
is your duty.
당신의 의무입니다.
If you fail to do this,
이를 수행하지 못하면
you are derelict in your duty.
당신은 의무를 소홀히 하고 있습니다.
In the future, when you encounter
앞으로
a similar situation,
비슷한 상황
prepare for both eventualities.
두 가지 경우 모두에 대비하세요.
I got it.
알겠어요.
I didn't think it through this time.
이번에는 생각지도 못했어요.
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
Go deal with it now.
지금 가서 처리하세요.
Hurry up.
서둘러요.
[Photos and videos]
[사진 및 동영상]
[Loading]
[로드 중]
[Handling]
[처리]
[Photos and videos]
[사진 및 동영상]
[It's easier to be recommended with description.]
[추천받기가 더 쉬워졌습니다. 설명과 함께.]
[Li Bingyan's security pushing people]
[Li Bingyan의 보안이 사람들을 밀고 있다]
[Li Bingyan's security pushing people, Qiao Feifei fans being humiliated]
[Li Bingyan의 보안이 사람들을 밀고 있습니다. Qiao Feifei 팬들이 굴욕을 당하고 있습니다]
Stop recording!
녹음을 중지하세요!
Why did you push me?
왜 나를 밀어냈나요?
Li Bingyan is going to be dropped by the show.
리빙옌이 가겠다 쇼에서 탈락합니다.
This is the internal notice document.
내부공지문입니다.
It will be announced this week.
이번 주에 발표될 예정입니다.
Two of Li Bingyan's brand endorsements
Li Bingyan의 브랜드 보증 두 가지
are reportedly going to be replaced as well.
에 갈 예정이라고 한다 교체도 됩니다.
Her agency is going to sue our Purong Hotel.
그녀의 소속사는 우리 푸롱 호텔을 고소하세요.
Ms. Xu,
쉬 선생님,
what should we do?
우리는 무엇을 해야 합니까?
Sue our hotel?
우리 호텔을 고소해?
Is it that serious?
그게 그렇게 심각한가요?
Back then,
그때는
when I invited Qiao Feifei to stay
내가 Qiao Feifei를 머물도록 초대했을 때
at our Purong Hotel,
저희 푸롱 호텔에서
I waited outside her manager's door, without food or drink,
나는 그녀의 매니저 문 밖에서 기다렸다. 음식이나 음료 없이
for two whole nights.
이틀 밤 동안.
What did I do it for?
내가 무엇을 위해 그랬습니까?
Don't I just want to bring glory
난 단지 영광을 돌리고 싶은 것 뿐이지 않아
to our Purong Hotel?
우리 푸롱 호텔로 가나요?
It's the critical stage for sales performance,
결정적인 단계다 판매 실적에 대해서는
yet such a bad incident happened in the presidential suite.
그런데 이런 안 좋은 사건이 일어났어요 대통령 스위트 룸에서.
Ms. Xu,
쉬 선생님,
do you have no sense of responsibility
너는 책임감이 없니
towards our hotel at all?
우리 호텔쪽으로 전혀?
I will solve my own problems.
나는 내 자신의 문제를 해결할 것입니다.
You don't need to put on a show for others here.
그럴 필요는 없습니다 여기에서 다른 사람들을 위해 쇼를 열어보세요.
Put on a show?
쇼를 하시겠습니까?
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
Ms. Lu,
루 선생님,
go about your business first.
먼저 당신의 사업을 시작하십시오.
Ms. Xu and I
Xu 선생님과 나
will discuss the follow-up work arrangements.
후속조치를 논의할 예정이다 작업 준비.
Okay, Mr. Ji.
알았어, 지 씨.
If you need me later,
나중에 제가 필요하면
I will go all out.
나는 모두 나가겠습니다.
I am sorry, Mr. Ji.
죄송해요, 지 선생님.
I didn't expect this
이건 예상하지 못했어
would have such a big impact on the hotel.
호텔에 큰 영향을 미칠 것입니다.
I will try my best
최선을 다하겠습니다
to solve it.
그것을 해결하기 위해.
I will go find Li Bingyan right now.
지금 당장 리빙옌을 찾으러 갈게요.
I'll wait for your results.
나는 당신의 결과를 기다릴 것입니다.
Okay.
좋아요.
Hello.
안녕하세요.
Excuse me,
죄송합니다.
is Ms. Li Bingyan here?
Li Bingyan 선생님이 여기 계시나요?
She is not here.
그녀는 여기에 없습니다.
You are?
당신은?
I'm her lawyer.
나는 그녀의 변호사입니다.
You can tell me anything.
당신은 나에게 무엇이든 말해 줄 수 있습니다.
Well,
음,
I would like
나는 원한다
to ask
물어보려면
if you could withdraw the lawsuit against our hotel.
철회할 수 있다면 우리 호텔을 상대로 소송을 제기했습니다.
We can discuss
우리는 토론할 수 있어요
and face any issues together.
어떤 문제라도 함께 직면해 보세요.
Say no more.
더 이상 말하지 마세요.
Ms. Li Bingyan is currently caught in a public opinion storm.
Li Bingyan 씨는 현재 체포되었습니다 여론 폭풍 속에서.
She is suffering heavy losses.
그녀는 큰 손실을 입고 있습니다.
She has entrusted me and my legal team
그녀는 나와 내 법무팀을 맡겼다
with full authority to protect her rights and interests.
모든 권한을 가지고 그녀의 권리와 이익을 보호하기 위해.
Your Purong Hotel's poor management
푸롱 호텔의 관리 상태가 좋지 않음
has damaged my client's reputation
내 고객의 평판을 손상시켰어요
and stalled her career.
그녀의 경력을 중단했습니다.
We are still in the stage of collecting evidence.
우리는 아직은 그런 단계에 있다. 증거 수집.
We will contact your hotel's legal department later.
귀하의 호텔에 연락드리겠습니다. 나중에 법무 부서.
If you have any questions,
질문이 있으시면
we can communicate at the hearing.
우리는 청문회에서 의사소통을 할 수 있습니다.
Sir!
선생님!
[You're my love.]
[당신은 내 사랑이에요.]
What's the matter,
무슨 일이야?
Butler Xu?
쑤 집사?
Hello, David.
안녕, 데이빗.
It's like this.
이렇습니다.
What happened yesterday
어제 무슨 일이 있었나요
has gotten out of control on the internet.
인터넷 통제가 불가능해졌습니다.
I know you have your considerations,
당신이 고려사항이 있다는 걸 알아요,
but it has affected our hotel's
하지만 그것이 우리 호텔에 영향을 미쳤어요
normal operation.
정상 작동.
The other party wants to sue us.
상대방이 우리를 고소하려고 합니다.
So,
그래서,
I want to ask,
묻고 싶어요
can you
할 수 있어?
ask Feifei to tell her fans
Feifei에게 팬들에게 전해달라고 부탁해
to calm down a little bit?
조금 진정하려고?
Calm down?
진정하다?
I'm so angry.
너무 화가 났어요.
Bullying my fans is bullying me.
팬들을 괴롭히는 것은 나를 괴롭히는 것이다.
I won't give up!
나는 포기하지 않을 것이다!
Alright, Feifei.
알았어, 페이페이.
We have a magazine shoot
잡지 촬영이 있어요
this afternoon.
오늘 오후.
You won't look pretty if you're angry.
화를 내면 예뻐 보이지 않을 것입니다.
Go change your clothes.
가서 옷을 갈아입으세요.
Go on.
계속하세요.
As for what happened yesterday,
어제 무슨 일이 있었는지에 관해서는
strictly speaking,
엄밀히 말하면
it has nothing to do with us.
그것은 우리와 아무 관련이 없습니다.
So we really can't help.
그래서 우리는 정말로 도울 수 없습니다.
Sorry.
죄송합니다.
Ms. Xu.
쉬 씨.
What's wrong?
무슨 일이야?
The guest in 1906 left this for you.
1906년 손님이 이것을 당신에게 남겼습니다.
Mr. Tan left?
탄 씨가 떠났나요?
Mr. Tan!
탄 씨!
-The program team has made an appointment. -Mr. Tan!
-프로그램팀에서 약속을 잡았습니다. -씨. 탠 껍질!
Okay, come with me.
좋아, 나랑 같이 가자
Mr. Tan!
탄 씨!
Ms. Xu.
쉬 씨.
I can't accept this.
나는 이것을 받아들일 수 없다.
Do you want to open it and take a look first?
열어 보시겠어요? 먼저 살펴볼까요?
I got this sample
이 샘플을 받았어요
from a friend.
친구에게서.
It's handmade,
손수 만든 거야
and the materials aren't expensive.
그리고 재료도 비싸지 않아요.
I just want to give it to you
그냥 너한테 주고 싶어
to express my feelings.
내 감정을 표현하기 위해.
No pressure this time, right?
이번에는 압박감이 없겠죠?
It's so beautiful.
너무 아름다워요.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
I'll accept it.
나는 그것을 받아들일 것이다.
I'm glad you like it.
마음에 드셨다니 기쁘네요.
There is something in your hair.
당신의 머리카락에 뭔가가 있습니다.
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
It's okay.
괜찮아요.
I'll get going now.
이제 가겠습니다.
Have a safe trip.
안전한 여행 되세요.
Okay.
좋아요.
Mr. Ji.
지 씨.
Are you done with your work?
할 일은 끝났나요?
I went to look for Li Bingyan just now,
지금 막 Li Bingyan을 찾으러 갔어요
but I didn't see her.
하지만 나는 그녀를 보지 못했습니다.
You didn't see her?
그녀를 못 봤나요?
And that's it?
그게 다야?
Where is your mind at?
당신의 마음은 어디에 있나요?
Do you only have that one guest in your eyes?
그 손님만 계시나요? 당신의 눈에는?
I just went to see Mr. Tan off.
방금 탄 씨를 배웅하러 갔어요.
There's a huge issue
큰 문제가 있어
with the presidential suite.
프레지덴셜 스위트룸과 함께.
I've always believed in you
난 항상 당신을 믿어왔어
and bought you time to solve it.
그리고 그 문제를 해결할 시간을 벌었습니다.
And look at you.
그리고 당신을보세요.
Instead of hurrying up to figure something out,
서두르는 대신 뭔가 알아내려고
you're receiving gifts from a guest.
당신은 손님으로부터 선물을 받고 있습니다.
Do you think
네 생각엔
fawning over one guest all day
하루 종일 손님 한 명에게 아첨하는 것
will secure your position?
당신의 지위를 확보할 것인가?
There are plenty of people waiting to take your spot.
사람이 많아요 자리를 차지하기를 기다리고 있습니다.
Tell me if you want to quit.
그만두고 싶으면 말해주세요.
Why did you...
왜 그랬어...
Ms. Li!
리씨!
Ms. Li,
리 씨,
I am here on behalf of Purong Hotel.
저는 푸롱 호텔을 대표하여 여기에 왔습니다.
I request that you withdraw the lawsuit against our hotel.
철회를 요청합니다 우리 호텔을 상대로 소송을 제기했습니다.
Let's face the media together.
함께 언론을 만나봅시다.
okay?
좋아요?
We?
우리?
Is there a common ground
공통점이 있나요
between you and me?
너와 나 사이?
We are your service provider.
우리는 귀하의 서비스 제공자입니다.
We have always
우리는 항상
handled problems from your perspective.
당신의 관점에서 문제를 처리했습니다.
What's more, during this period,
게다가 이 기간 동안
haven't we been getting along well?
우리 잘 지내지 않았어?
Playing the emotional card?
감정 카드를 사용하고 있습니까?
Please take a good look at the target.
대상을 잘 살펴보시기 바랍니다.
There is only an employment relationship between us,
고용관계만 있을 뿐 우리 사이
not a friendship.
우정이 아닙니다.
Your hotel provided hellish service.
귀하의 호텔은 지옥 같은 서비스를 제공했습니다.
Now that something went wrong, you still want me to be lenient?
이제 뭔가 잘못됐으니, 아직도 내가 관대해지기를 바라나요?
What a joke.
정말 농담이에요.
Ms. Li,
리 씨,
right after the incident,
사건 직후
the hotel sent security personnel
호텔에서 보안요원을 보냈어요
to handle the situation.
상황을 처리하기 위해.
Besides,
게다가,
it wasn't the hotel you actually clashed with,
그 호텔은 아니었어 당신은 실제로
but the fans who trespassed onto the presidential suite floor.
하지만 무단 침입한 팬들은 프레지덴셜 스위트층.
Logically speaking,
논리적으로 말하면,
you shouldn't be suing the hotel.
호텔을 고소하면 안 됩니다.
Of course, I understand
물론이죠, 이해해요
that the agency wants to use the hotel as a megaphone
소속사가 원하는 것 호텔을 메가폰으로 사용해
to amplify this matter.
이 문제를 확대하기 위해.
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
Are you making excuses to shift the blame?
책임을 전가하기 위해 변명을 하고 있습니까?
Your hotel's management loopholes
호텔 관리상의 허점
caused such a huge conflict
엄청난 갈등을 일으켰어
and damaged my reputation.
그리고 내 평판을 손상시켰습니다.
Now you want to wash your hands of it
이제 손을 씻고 싶군요
and avoid taking responsibility?
그리고 책임을 회피하는가?
And another thing.
그리고 또 다른 것.
You're just a floor forewoman.
당신은 단지 현장 감독일 뿐입니다.
How can you talk to me about an equal position?
어떻게 나한테 말을 할 수 있어? 동등한 위치에 대해?
Who do you think you are?
당신은 누구라고 생각합니까?
Getting along well?
잘 지내고 있나요?
Do you deserve it?
당신은 그럴 자격이 있나요?
Go back and tell your general manager
돌아가서 총책임자에게 말하세요
to get the best lawyer right away.
최고의 변호사를 바로 구하려면.
Let's
하자
see in court.
법정에서 보세요.
Wait a minute!
잠깐 기다려요!
Ms. Li.
리 씨.
Do I need to remind you?
상기시켜야 하나요?
A couple of days ago,
며칠 전,
when they were filming at the VIP entrance,
그들이 촬영할 때 VIP 입구에서,
you intentionally brought your boyfriend
넌 의도적으로 남자친구를 데려왔어
and showed up there, right?
그리고 거기 나타났지, 그렇지?
I reminded you the day before
전날 상기시켜 줬어요
that during that time,
그 시간 동안
the program crew will be filming at the VIP entrance,
프로그램 제작진 VIP 입구에서 촬영할 예정이에요
and there will be media.
그리고 미디어가 있을 것이다.
But you just had to show up at that specific time.
하지만 넌 그래야만 했어 그 특정 시간에 나타나세요.
Didn't you just use me, a lowly forewoman,
방금 저 하급 감독인 나를 이용하지 않았나요?
to get the information,
정보를 얻으려면
then direct and act in
그런 다음 지시하고 행동하세요
an attention-grabbing drama,
주목받는 드라마
and finally push the responsibility for poor arrangements
그리고 마침내 책임을 밀어붙인다 좋지 않은 준비를 위해
onto our hotel?
우리 호텔로?
Isn't that right?
그렇지 않나요?
What are you trying to say?
무슨 말을 하려는 걸까요?
That being troubled by Qiao Feifei's fans
Qiao Feifei의 팬들이 고민하고 있는 것
is my own fault?
내 잘못인가?
That's not what I meant.
내 말은 그런 뜻이 아니다.
I came to see you today
오늘 너를 만나러 왔어요
not to discuss who is right or wrong,
누가 옳고 그른지 논의하지 마세요
but to ask you to rationally consider
하지만 합리적으로 고려해 달라고 요청하는 건
your current situation.
당신의 현재 상황.
Right.
오른쪽.
Although I am just a lowly forewoman,
나는 비록 하찮은 감독일 뿐이지만,
on an executive level,
경영진 수준에서는
I am the spokesperson for the hotel.
저는 호텔 대변인입니다.
Today I'm here on behalf of the hotel
오늘 저는 호텔을 대신하여 여기에 왔습니다
to discuss a way forward with you.
당신과 앞으로 나아갈 길을 논의하기 위해.
In short,
즉,
if you withdraw the lawsuit against the hotel,
당신이 철수한다면 호텔을 상대로 한 소송,
the rewards you receive will be substantial.
당신이 받는 보상 상당할 것입니다.
The hotel won't have to put more energy
호텔은 더 이상 에너지를 투입할 필요가 없을 것입니다
into dealing with this unreasonable lawsuit.
~을 다루다 이 불합리한 소송.
Then,
그러면
we can definitely,
확실히 할 수 있어,
with the attitude and sincerity of an ally,
태도로 그리고 동맹국의 성실함,
help defend you in public
공개적으로 당신을 변호하는 데 도움을 주세요
and recover your losses.
그리고 손실을 복구하십시오.
However,
그러나
if you fail to appreciate the hotel's good intentions
감사하지 못한다면 호텔의 좋은 의도
and choose to bite the hand that feeds you,
그리고 물기를 선택 당신에게 먹이를 주는 손
then this lawsuit is bound to be a protracted one.
그럼 이번 소송은 장기화될 수밖에 없습니다.
And both sides will suffer.
그리고 양측 모두 고통을 겪을 것입니다.
Setting aside our hotel's losses,
호텔의 손실을 제쳐두고,
during this time,
이 시간 동안
you may face a damaged reputation,
평판이 훼손될 수 있습니다.
career stagnation,
경력 정체,
and fleeting popularity.
그리고 일시적인 인기.
How quickly the entertainment industry changes,
얼마나 빨리 연예계가 변하고
I think you know better than anyone.
누구보다 잘 아시는 것 같아요.
So,
그래서,
whether to cooperate with us or not,
우리와 협력할지 여부,
think clearly before you decide.
결정하기 전에 명확하게 생각하십시오.
You're just a floor forewoman.
당신은 단지 현장 감독일 뿐입니다.
How can you talk to me about a common position?
어떻게 나한테 말을 할 수 있어? 공통 입장에 대해?
Who do you think you are?
당신은 누구라고 생각합니까?
Getting along happily?
행복하게 지내고 있나요?
Do you deserve it?
당신은 그럴 자격이 있나요?
Ms. Xu,
쉬 선생님,
you impress me.
당신은 나에게 깊은 인상을 남겼습니다.
Li Bingyan's legal representative
Li Bingyan의 법률 대리인
sent me an email,
나에게 이메일을 보냈습니다.
saying their internal team
내부 팀이 말하는 것
needs to reconsider the litigation resolution.
다시 생각해 볼 필요가 있다 소송해결.
It seems your persuasion worked.
당신의 설득이 효과가 있었던 것 같습니다.
Good job.
잘했어요.
That's good.
좋아요.
Mr. Ji is not here.
지 씨는 여기 없어요.
Are you looking for him?
그를 찾고 있나요?
No.
아니요.
Regarding the hotel's losses,
호텔의 손실에 관해
Mr. Ji has already gone to figure out a way.
지씨는 이미 가버렸어요 방법을 알아내려고.
He will bring the program team's accommodation orders
그는 프로그램 팀의 숙박 주문
to the hotel
호텔로
to try to eliminate the negative impact.
부정적인 영향을 제거하려고 노력합니다.
This matter
이 문제
is considered over.
끝난 것으로 간주됩니다.
You don't need to blame yourself too much.
너무 자신을 비난할 필요는 없습니다.
After all, you were also drawn into
결국 당신도
this intrigue.
이 음모.
You handled it very well.
당신은 그것을 아주 잘 처리했습니다.
In the HSKP Department,
HSKP학과에서는
it's inevitable to encounter such things.
그런 일을 겪는 것은 불가피합니다.
Even if you are promoted in the future,
앞으로 승진하더라도
some things
몇 가지
will still require you to handle them personally.
여전히 당신이 필요합니다 개인적으로 처리하기 위해.
Consider this a trial.
이것을 재판이라고 생각하십시오.
Thank you, Mr. Xue.
감사합니다, 쉬에 씨.
I'll go back to work then.
그럼 저는 다시 일하러 갈게요.
Okay.
좋아요.
[HSKP Department of Purong Hotel ,Xu Miyu]
[푸롱 호텔 HSKP 부서, Xu Miyu]
Li Bingyan has yielded.
Li Bingyan이 양보했습니다.
Ms. Xu got it done.
Ms. Xu가 해냈습니다.
Do you think
네 생각엔
fawning over one guest all day
하루 종일 손님 한 명에게 아첨하는 것
will secure your position?
당신의 지위를 확보할 것인가?
There are plenty of people waiting to take your spot.
사람이 많아요 자리를 차지하기를 기다리고 있습니다.
If you want to quit,
그만두고 싶다면
tell me sooner.
더 빨리 말해주세요.
♪ A flicker of dim light ♪
♪ 희미한 빛의 깜박임 ♪
♪ A bowl of warm soup ♪
♪ 따뜻한 국 한 그릇 ♪
♪ People in the city ♪
♪ 도시의 사람들 ♪
♪ Squeezing into the hustle and bustle ♪
♪ 소란스러운 상황 속으로 비집고 들어갑니다 ♪
♪ The palms of time ♪
♪ 시간의 손바닥 ♪
♪ Grinding away the simple days ♪
♪ 단순한 일상을 날려버리세요 ♪
♪ Sprinkling them into this busy world ♪
♪ 바쁜 세상에 뿌려주세요 ♪
♪ To be tasted, bit by bit ♪
♪ 조금씩 맛볼 수 있도록 ♪
It was indeed my fault to begin with.
사실 처음부터 내 잘못이었다.
[Civil Complaint]
[민원신고]
I had some conflicts with the hotel,
호텔과 갈등이 좀 있었어요,
which led to some misunderstandings,
이로 인해 오해가 생겼습니다.
and even alerted the company's legal team.
회사 법무팀에도 알렸습니다.
Thinking about it now,
지금 생각해보면,
I am truly ashamed.
정말 부끄럽습니다.
Mr. Ji.
지 씨.
Bingyan,
빙옌,
long time no see.
오랜만이에요.
Regarding the extreme behavior of those fans,
극단적인 행동에 대해 그 팬들 중
the fan club has already stepped in
팬클럽이 이미 들어왔어
and severely criticized them.
그리고 그들을 신랄하게 비난했습니다.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Here.
여기.
Mr. Dai,
다이 씨,
thank you for your cooperation.
협조해 주셔서 감사합니다.
You are a reasonable man, Mr. Ji.
지 선생님은 합리적인 분이세요.
Technically speaking,
기술적으로 말하자면,
the troublemaking fans are not part of our company.
문제를 일으키는 팬들 우리 회사의 일부가 아닙니다.
This time, we are willing to cooperate in mediation
이번에는 협력할 의향이 있습니다. 중재 중
purely out of respect for Mr. Ji.
순전히 지씨에 대한 존경심에서요.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
But there is one thing I must make clear.
하지만 한 가지 분명히 짚고 넘어가야 할 것이 있습니다.
Please go ahead.
계속하세요.
I heard that
그 말 들었어
these fans went up
이 팬들이 올라갔어
with a guest
손님과 함께
who previously stayed in the presidential suite.
이전에 머물렀던 사람 대통령 스위트 룸에서.
the presidential suite.
대통령 스위트 룸.
Yes.
예.
We have checked the surveillance video.
감시 영상을 확인했습니다.
Then,
그러면
how do they know each other?
그들은 서로를 어떻게 아는가?
I also heard
나도 들었어
that the person who introduced them
그 사람을 소개한 사람
was the VIP manager of your sales department—
VIP 매니저였어 영업 부서의 —
Lu Zhenzhen.
루 젠젠.
I've dealt with her before.
나는 전에 그녀를 상대했습니다.
As long as it benefits her,
그것이 그녀에게 이익이 되는 한,
she would certainly
그 사람은 분명 그럴 거야
do something like this.
이런 일을하십시오.
[General Manager's Office]
[부장실]
Mr. Ji,
지 선생님,
do I need to communicate with Li Bingyan's side?
나랑 소통해야 해? 리빙옌 편?
How did Qiao Feifei's fans get to the presidential suite?
Qiao Feifei의 팬들은 어땠나요? 대통령 스위트룸에 가볼까?
I have no idea.
나는 모른다.
Didn't they come to you?
그들이 당신에게 오지 않았나요?
Weren't you the person in charge of the fan meeting?
당신은 그 사람이 아니었나요? 팬미팅 담당?
Mr. Ji,
지 선생님,
they asked me about Mr. Duan Jr.
Duan Jr. 씨에 대해 물었어요
I was also...
나도...
Did they ask about it
그들이 그것에 대해 물어봤나요
or did you leak it on purpose?
아니면 일부러 유출한 건가요?
Of course they asked.
물론 그들은 물었습니다.
Leaking a guest's information privately is a serious dereliction of duty.
투숙객의 정보를 비공개로 유출하는 행위 심각한 직무유기이다.
Are you clear on how it should be handled
Are you clear on how it should be handled
according to industry regulations?
어떻게 처리해야 하는지 명확히 알고 있나요
I'm sorry, Mr. Ji.
업계 규정에 따르면?
I was really pushed too far by them
죄송해요, 지 선생님.
and acted without thinking.
난 정말 그들에게 너무 밀렸어
Mr. Ji, you must give me a chance
그리고 생각 없이 행동했다.
to make up for it.
지 선생님, 저에게 기회를 주셔야 합니다
I happen to have a few major clients
그것을 만회하기 위해.
about to close.
나에겐 주요 고객이 몇 명 있다
I promise that this quarter,
곧 닫힐 예정입니다.
I can bring at least three large orders to the hotel.
이번 분기에는
Your bonus for one quarter will be deducted.
최소한 가지고 갈 수 있어요 호텔에 세 건의 대량 주문을 했습니다.
You said three large orders yourself.
한 분기 동안의 보너스 차감됩니다.
If you can't do it, you'll be fired.
당신은 세 가지 큰 주문을 직접 말했다.
Also,
당신이 그것을 할 수 없다면, 당신은 해고 될 것입니다.
I don't know what your habits were before,
또한,
but here,
이전에 당신의 습관이 어땠는지 모르겠어요,
stop playing dirty
하지만 여기서는
and taking shortcuts.
더러운 장난은 그만둬
Mr. Ji, I know I was wrong.
그리고 지름길을 택합니다.
I will never do it again.
지 선생님, 제가 틀렸다는 걸 압니다.
Mr. Zhao,
나는 다시는 그것을하지 않을 것입니다.
Purong Hotel is certainly very sincere.
자오 씨,
[Customer information Yinhe Zhichuang Exhibition Planning Group]
푸롱 호텔은 확실히 매우 성실합니다.
As for the specific terms,
[고객정보 Yinhe Zhichuang 전시 기획 그룹]
how about we set up a time to meet and talk?
구체적인 용어는
Tomorrow is fine for me, of course.
우리 준비하는 게 어때? 만나서 얘기할 시간?
Zhenzhen.
물론 내일은 괜찮습니다.
Mr. Zhao,
젠젠.
how about I visit your company personally tomorrow afternoon?
자오 씨,
Don't you know me?
내가 직접 너희 회사를 방문하는 게 어때? 내일 오후?
We've known each other for so long.
당신은 나를 모르나요?
I will definitely give you the best plan.
우리는 오랫동안 서로를 알고 있었습니다.
Zhenzhen.
반드시 최선의 계획을 제시해 드리겠습니다.
Okay.
젠젠.
Okay, Mr. Zhao, see you tomorrow.
좋아요.
[Approval] [Lu Zhenzhen's outing request]
좋아요, 자오 씨, 내일 뵙겠습니다.
Why did you drink so much?
[승인] [루진전 외출 요청]
Didn't you see I was on the phone?
왜 그렇게 많이 마셨나요?
I had a social engagement tonight.
내가 통화하고 있는 거 못 봤어?
I drank a little too much.
오늘 밤에 사교 모임을 가졌습니다.
Then you should get some rest.
나는 술을 조금 과하게 마셨다.
I still have to work overtime for a while.
그럼 좀 쉬어야지.
Can you cook some porridge for me?
아직 한동안 야근을 해야 해요.
My stomach is not feeling well.
나를 위해 죽을 좀 끓여줄 수 있나요?
Can you just order some takeout yourself?
속이 안 좋아지네요.
Won't the takeout be cold by the time it arrives?
직접 테이크아웃을 주문할 수 있나요?
Nie Yucheng,
테이크아웃은 춥지 않을까 도착할 때쯤에는?
I'm not your mother.
니 유쳉,
Ji Feng keeps an eye on me every day now.
나는 당신의 어머니가 아닙니다.
I'm under a lot of pressure at work.
Ji Feng은 이제 매일 나를 지켜보고 있습니다.
If you think I can't serve you well,
나는 직장에서 많은 스트레스를 받고 있습니다.
I'll get you a nanny, okay?
내가 당신을 잘 섬길 수 없다고 생각한다면,
Okay.
내가 유모를 구해줄게, 알았지?
You get back to work. Okay.
좋아요.
The medicine is in the living room drawer.
당신은 다시 일을 시작합니다. 좋아요.
Hurry, give me the bowl.
약은 거실 서랍에 있어요.
It smells so good.
냄새가 너무 좋아요.
This is the newly arrived Nanhui salted meat.
이게 새로 도착한 거야 난휘소금고기.
The quality is excellent.
품질이 우수합니다.
Judging by your look, it's in the bag.
표정으로 보면 가방 안에 있는 것 같아요.
It's almost a done deal.
거의 완료된 거래입니다.
Have a taste. How is it?
맛보세요. 어때요?
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Wait.
기다리다.
I suggest
나는 제안한다
you take a sip of soup first
먼저 수프를 한 모금 마셔
to open up your taste buds,
미각을 열어드리기 위해
and then eat the food.
그리고 음식을 먹습니다.
So particular.
정말 특별해요.
Alright, I'll listen to you.
알았어, 내가 들어줄게.
You should taste it first.
먼저 맛을 봐야 합니다.
Your head is almost falling into the soup bowl.
머리가 거의 수프 그릇에 빠지다.
No, no, no.
아니, 아니, 아니.
You... you taste it first.
너... 네가 먼저 맛봐.
How is it?
어때요?
Is it not good?
좋지 않은가?
Let me taste it.
맛보게 해주세요.